A Guide to the University of Virginia Hospital Executive Director's Office (HEDO) Collection
Claude Moore Health Sciences Library
- BARRINGER WING ADDITION, UVA HOSPITAL, CHARLOTTESVILLE, VA, ADDENDUM NO. 3 Janaury 7, 1953, TMs (Box-folder 15:026)
  PROJECT SPECIFICATIONS
- ADDITION TO BARRINGER WING, UVA HOSPITAL January 8, 1953, TL, TMs (Box-folder 15:027)
  CONTRACTS AND BIDS
- CONSTRUCTION OF BARRINGER WING ADDITION CORRESPONDENCE May - August 1954, TL, TLS (2) (Box-folder 15:028)
- ADDITION TO BARRINGER WING: SUMMARY OF LOW BIDS January 22, 1953, TMs (Box-folder 15:029)
- INSPECTION OF UVA HOSPITAL, BARRINGER ADDITION October 1, 1954, TMs (Box-folder 15:030)
- INSPECTION OF UVA HOSPITAL, BARRINGER ADDITION October 8, 1954, TMs (Box-folder 15:031)
- INSPECTION OF UVA HOSPITAL, BARRINGER ADDITION November 9, 1954, TMs (Box-folder 15:032)
- INSPECTION OF UVA HOSPITAL, BARRINGER ADDITION December 1954, TL, TMs (Box-folder 15:033)
- INSPECTION OF BARRINGER WING ADDITION December 22, 1954, TMs (Box-folder 15:034)
- CONSTRUCTION OF BARRINGER WING ADDITION: VARIOUS ESTIMATES & CONTRACT DATA January 24, 1955, TMs (Box-folder 15:035)
- CONSTRUCTION CORRESPONDENCE WITH BASKERVILLE & SONS, ARCHITECTS 1954 - 1963, TL, TLS (2) (Box-folder 15:036)
- CONSTRUCTION OF HOSPITAL BUILDING COMMITTEE CORRESPONDENCE 1949 - 1960, TL, TMs, TLS (2) (Box-folder 15:037)
- CONSTRUCTION: BUREAU OF HOSPITAL SURVEY & CONSTRUCTION CORRESPONDENCE AND QUESTIONNAIRE 1951, TL, TMs, TLS (Box-folder 15:038)
- CONSTRUCTION OF CANCER RESEARCH ADDITION CORRESPONDENCE 1951 - 1957, TL, TLS (2) (Box-folder 15:039)
- CONSTRUCTION OF CANCER RESEARCH ADDITION CORRESPONDENCE March - June 1958, TL, TLS (2), TMs (Box-folder 15:040)
- CONSTRCUTION OF CANCER RESEARCH ADDITION CORRESPONDENCE July - August 1958, TL, TLS (Box-folder 15:041)
- CONSTRUCTION OF CANCER RESEARCH ADDITION CORRESPONDENCE September - December 1958, TL, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 15:042)
- CONSTRUCTION OF CANCER RESEARCH ADDITION, CHANGE ORDER CORRESPONDENCE 1958 - 1959, TL (Box-folder 15:043)
- CONSTRUCTION OF CANCER RESEARCH ADDITION CORRESPONDENCE 1959 - 1960, TL, TLS (2), TMs (Box-folder 15:044)
- SITE INSPECTION -OLD ADMINISTRATION WING (PRIOR TO UNDERPINNING), CANCER RESEARCH BUILDING August 1958, TL, TMs (Box-folder 15:045)
- SITE INSPECTION OF OLD ADMINISTRATION WING (PRIOR TO UNDERPINNING), CANCER RESEARCH BUILDING August 1958, TL, TMs (Box-folder 15:045)
- CONSTRUCTION OF CANCER RESEARCH ADDITION COSTS: CORRESPONDENCE, ESTIMATES AND COST DATA 1958 - 1960, TL, TLS, AMs (Box-folder 15:046)
- CONSTRUCTION - ALTERATIONS AND ADDITIONS: CORRESPONDENCE 1954 - 1963, TMs, TL, TLS (2) (Box-folder 15:047)
- CONSTRUCTION - CAPITAL OUTLAY EQUIPMENT CORRESPONDENCE August 3, 1960, TLS (Box-folder 15:048)
- CONSTRUCTION- CAPITAL OUTLAY STUDY 1970, TMs (Box-folder 15:049)
- CONSTRUCTION-CENTRAL STERILE SUPPLY CORRESPONDENCE 1955, TL, TLS (Box-folder 15:050)
- CONSTRUCTION OF CENTRAL SUPPLY AUTOCLAVING ROOM ONE-STORY OFFICE ADDITION H 1954 - 1956, TL (Box-folder 15:051)
- CONSTRUCTION OF DAVIS WING CORRESPONDENCE 1954 - 1959, TL, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 15:052)
- CONSTRUCTION OF CLINICAL DEPARTMENTS OFFICE BUILDING CORRESPONDENCE May 8, 1962, TLS (Box-folder 15:053)
- CONSTRUCTION OF CLINICAL LABORATORY CORRESPONDENCE July 6, 1960, TL (Box-folder 15:054)
- CONSTRUCTION OF COBB CHEMISTRY BUILDING CORRESPONDENCE 1966 - 1969, TL, TLS (2), AMs (Box-folder 15:055)
- CONSTRUCTION COMMITTEE ON LABORATORY SPACE October 2, 1956, TMs (Box-folder 15:056)
- CONSTRUCTION OF CONFERENCE MEMORANDA 1959 - 1960, TL, TMs, TLS (Box-folder 15:057)
- CONSTRUCTION CONTRACTS 1945, 1955, 1959, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 15:058)
- CONSTRUCTION COSTS CORRESPONDENCE AND SUMMARIES 1949 - 1958, AL, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 15:059)
- CONSTRUCTION: EGGERS & HIGGINS--ARCHITECTS 1949 - 1957, TL, TLS (2), leaflet (Box-folder 16:001)
  CORRESPONDENCE
- CONSTRUCTION REPORT SHEETS: EGGERS & HIGGINS, ARCHITECTS 1955 - 1956, TMs (Box-folder 16:002)
- CONSTRUCTION TRANSMISSION OF DRAWING FORMS: EGGERS & HIGGINS, ARCHITECTS 1956, Printed forms w/ autographed additions (Box-folder 16:003)
- CONSTRUCTION EQUIPMENT: CORRESPONDENCE 1953 - 1960, TL, ANS, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 16:004)
- CONSTRUCTION OF EXPERIMENTAL NUCLEAR REACTOR: CORRESPONDENCE 1957, TL (Box-folder 16:005)
- FINAL ESTIMATES OF CONSTRUCTION COSTS May 8, 1957, TMs (Box-folder 16:006)
- CONSTRUCTION FIRE-PROFFING AND REMODELING: CORRESPONDENCE July 10, 1961, TL (Box-folder 16:007)
- FOUNDATION INVESTIGATION FOR UVA June 1957, TMs (Box-folder 16:008)
- CONSTRUCTION GENERAL FUND APPROPRIATIONS, BIENNIUM 1954-56, TMs (Box-folder 16:009)
- CONSTRUCTION CORRESPONDENCE FOR HILL-BURTON PROGRAM 1948 - 1957, TL, TLS (2) (Box-folder 16:010)
- PROPOSED REVISIONS IN HILL BURTON PROJECT NO. 51-586 August 1954, TMs (Box-folder 16:011)
  FROM HILL-BURTON FILE
- CONSTRUCTION OF HILL-BURTON PROGRAM 1953 - 1955, Pamphlets (2), Leaflets (2) (Box-folder 16:012)
- CONSTRUCTION OF HOSPITAL EXPANSION PLAN NO. 2: CORRESPONDENCE August 6, 1953, TLS (Box-folder 16:013)
- CONSTRUCTION INSURANCE CORRESPONDENCE March 17, 1958, TL (Box-folder 16:014)
- CONSTRUCTION OF KITCHEN: CORRESPONDENCE 1948 - 1954, TL, TLS (2) (Box-folder 16:015)
- JITCHEN CONSTRUCTION: CORRESPONDENCE August 1954, TL, TLS (2), TMs (Box-folder 16:016)
- JITCHEN CONSTRUCTION: CORRESPONDENCE December 1954-August 1963, TL, TLS (2) (Box-folder 16:017)
- COMMITTEE MINUTES ON HOSPITAL KITCHEN ADDITION 1949 - 1950, TMs (Box-folder 16:018)
- ESTIMATE FOR HOSPITAL KITCHEN ADDITION May 3, 1954, TMs (Box-folder 16:019)
- CONTRACTORS' BIDS FOR CONSTRUCTION OF MAIN KITCHEN AND CAFETERIA July 1954 - August 1954, TL, AMs, TMs (Box-folder 16:020)
  INCLUDES COST ESTIMATES AND COVER LETTERS
- MAIN KITCHEN AND CAFETERIA, UVA HOSPITAL, ADDENDUM 3 August 14, 1954, TMs (Box-folder 16:021)
  RE: CHANGES IN CONSTRUCTION PLANS
- LIBRARY CONSTRUCTION COMMITTEE MINUTES, TMs (Box-folder 16:022)
- LINEN ROOM CONSTRUCTION CORRESPONDENCE 1951 - 1953, TL, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 16:023)
- PROPOSED BUILDING PROGRAM: UVA HOSPITAL August 1953, TMs (Box-folder 16:024)
  FROM CONSTRUCTION -LONG-TERM BUILDING FILE
- CONSTRUCTION OF MASTER PLAN COMMITTEE MINUTES July 6, 1960, TMs (Box-folder 16:025)
- CONSTRUCTION ESTIMATES FOR MEDICAL LIBRARY May 12, 1965, TMs (Box-folder 16:026)
- CONSTRUCTION OF MULTI-STORY ADDITION: CORRESPONDENCE March 1953 - 1954, TL (2), TLS (2), TMs (Box-folder 16:027)
- CONSTRUCTION OF MULTISTORY ADDITION CORRESPONDENCE April 1954-September 1954, TL (2), TLS (2) (Box-folder 16:028)
- CONSTRUCTION OF MULTI-STORY ADDITION CORRESPONDENCE October 1954- August 1955, TL, TLS (2) (Box-folder 16:029)
- CONSTRUCTION OF MULTISTORY ADDITION: CORRESPONDENCE September - December 1955, TL, TLS (2), Telegram (Box-folder 16:030)
- CONSTRUCTION OF MULTI-STORY ADDITION CORRESPONDENCE January - February 1956, TL, TLS (2) (Box-folder 16:031)
- CONSTRUCTION OF MULTI-STORY ADDITION: CORRESPONDENCE March 1956 - April 1956, TL, TLS (2) (Box-folder 16:032)
- CONSTRUCTION OF MULTI-STORY ADDITION CORRESPONDENCE May 1956 - June 1956, TL, TLS (2) (Box-folder 16:033)
- CONSTRUCTION OF MULTI-STORY ADDITION CORRESPONDENCE July 1956 - August 1956, TL, TLS (2) (Box-folder 16:034)
- CONSTRUCTION OF MULTI-STORY ADDITION CORRESPONDENCE September - November 1956, TL, TLS (2) (Box-folder 16:035)
- CONSTRUCTION OF MULTI-STORY ADDITION: CORRESPONDENCE December 1956-January1957, TL, TLS (2) (Box-folder 16:036)
- CONSTRUCTION OF MUTLI-STORY ADDITION CORRESPONDENCE February - April 1957, TL, TLS (2) (Box-folder 16:037)
- CONSTRUCTION OF MULTI-STORY ADDITION: CORRESPONDENCE May 1957 - July 1957, TL, TLS (2) (Box-folder 16:038)
- CONSTRUCTION OF MULTI-STORY ADDITION: CORRESPONDENCE August - October 1957, TL, TLS (2) (Box-folder 16:039)
- CONSTRUCTION OF MULTI-STORY ADDITION: CORRESPONDENCE November - December 1957, TL, TLS (2) (Box-folder 16:040)
- CONSTRUCTION OF MULTI-STORY ADDITION: CORRESPONDENCE January - February 1958, TL, TLS (2), TMs (Box-folder 16:041)
- CONSTRUCTION OF MULTI-STORY BUILDING CORRESPONDENCE March 1958 - April 1958, TL, TLS (2) (Box-folder 16:042)
- CONSTRUCTION OF MULTI-STORY ADDITION: CORRESPONDENCE May 1958 - June 1958, TL, TLS (2), TMs (Box-folder 16:043)
- CONSTRUCTION OF MULTI-STORY ADDITION: CORRESPONDENCE July 1958- September 1958, TL, TLS (2) (Box-folder 16:044)
- CONSTRUCTION OF MULTI-STORY ADDITION: CORRESPONDENCE October - December 1958, TL, TLS (2), TMs (Box-folder 16:045)
- CONSTRUCTION OF MULTI-STORY ADDITION: CORRESPONDENCE January - February 1959, TL, TLS (2), TMs (Box-folder 16:046)
- CONSTRUCTION OF MULTI-STORY ADDITION: CORRESPONDENCE March 1959 - May 1959, TL, TLS (Box-folder 16:047)
- CONSTRUCTION OF MULTI-STORY ADDITION: CORRESPONDENCE June 1954 - July 1954, TLS, TL (2) (Box-folder 16:048)
- CONSTRUCTION OF MULTI-STORY ADDITION: CORRESPONDENCE August - November 1959, TL, TLS (Box-folder 16:049)
- CONSTRUCTION OF MULTI-STORY ADDITION: CORRESPONDENCE December 1959, TL, TLS (2), TMs (Box-folder 16:050)
- CONSTRUCTION OF MULTI-STORY ADDITION: CORRESPONDENCE January 1960 - March 1960, TL, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 16:051)
- CONSTRUCTION OF MULTI-STORY ADDITION: CORRESPONDENCE April 1960 - July 1960, TL, TLS (Box-folder 16:052)
- CONSTRUCTION OF MULTI-STORY ADDITION: CORRESPONDENCE August - December 1960, TL, TLS (Box-folder 16:053)
- CONSTRUCTION OF MULTI-STORY ADDITION: CORRESPONDENCE February - September 1961, TL, TLS (2) (Box-folder 16:054)
- CONSTRUCTION OF MULTI-STORY ADDITION: CORRESPONDENCE October - December 1961, TL, TLS (2) (Box-folder 16:055)
- CONSTRUCTION OF MULTI-STORY ADDITION: CORRESPONDENCE 1962, TL, TLS (2) (Box-folder 16:056)
- MEETING IN CONNECTION W/ PROPOSED MULTI-STORY HOSPITAL March 11, 1954, TMs (Box-folder 17:001)
- MULTI-STOREY HOSPITAL July 12, 1954, TMs (Box-folder 17:002)
- REPORT ON MEETING TO DECIDE LOCATION OF AIR CONDITIONING EQUIPMENT October 18, 1955, TMs (Box-folder 17:003)
  RE: MULTI-STOREY ADDITION TO UVA HOSPITAL
- SUGGESTIONS FROM NURSING SERVICE CONCERNING THE PLANS FOR THE HOSPITAL ADDITION December 1955 - Feb. 1956, TMs (Box-folder 17:004)
- SUGGESTIONS FOR THE NEW MULTI-STOREY ADDITION May 1956 - June 1956, TMs (Box-folder 17:005)
- MULTI-STOREY ADDITION, A/C/ LOADS February 1957, TMs (Box-folder 17:006)
  RE: USAGE OF NEW BUILDING/PATIENTS OR STAFF PER ROOM
- PART III OF THE CONSTRUCTION APPLICATION FOR MULTI-STOREY ADDITION October 1957 - Nov. 1957, TMs, TL (2), TLS (2) (Box-folder 17:007)
  INCLUDES SITE DESCRIPTION
- FORM OF BID BOND January 8, 1958, Doc (Box-folder 17:008)
- BID FORM FROM AMERICAN STERILIZER CO. Janaury 29, 1958, TMs (Box-folder 17:009)
- ADDENDA # 3-4, COMMISSION, MULTI-STOREY ADDITION TO HOSPITAL BY ARCHITECTS January - February 1958, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 17:010)
- STANDARD PERFORMABLE BONDS February 1958, Doc. (Box-folder 17:011)
- FORM OF AGREEMENT FOR UVA HOSPITAL February 13, 1958, Doc (Box-folder 17:012)
- SCHEDULE OF VALUES March 1958, TL, TMs (Box-folder 17:013)
  ITEMIZED COST LISTED BY ARCHITECTS
- ESTIMATE OF TOTAL ARCHITECTS' FEES FOR PROPOSED ADDITION, UVA HOSPITAL No Date, TMs (Box-folder 17:014)
- OUTLINE SPECIFICATION: MULTI-STOREY ADDITION TO UVA HOSPITAL March 1957, TMs (Box-folder 17:015)
- GROUP II & III EQUIPMENT LIST, PROJECT # VA.-93: MULTI-STOREY ADDITION TO UVA HOSPITAL 1960, TL, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 17:016)
- CONSTRUCTION OF MULTI-STOREY ADDITION, AIR-CONDITIONING: MISC. CORRESPONDENCE 1955 - 1961, TL, TLS (2) (Box-folder 17:017)
- CONSTRUCTION OF MULTI-STOREY ADDITION, ALLOTMENTS: CORRESPONDENCE AND REPORTS 1958 - 1960, TL, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 17:018)
- APPLICATION FOR APPROVAL OF AWARD OF CONTRACTS February 1958, TLS (2), TMs (Box-folder 17:019)
- CONSTRUCTION OF MULTI-STOREY ADDITION, APPLICATION FOR APPROVAL OF PRELIMINARY DESIGNS: CORRESPONDENCE 1956 - 1957, TL (2), TMs (Box-folder 17:020)
- CONSTRUCTION OF MULTI-STOREY ADDITION, APPLICATION FOR WORKING DRAWINGS AND SPECIFICATIONS December 1957, TLS, TMs, AMs (Box-folder 17:021)
- CONSTRUCTION OF MULTI-STOREY ADDITION, ART COMMISION: CORRESPONDENCE 1956 - 1962, TL (2), TLS (3) (Box-folder 17:022)
- CONSTRUCTION OF MULTI-STOREY ADDITION: CORRESPONDENCE 1958 - 1960, TL (2), TLS (2) (Box-folder 17:023)
- CONSTRUCTION OF MULTI-STOREY ADDITION, BID TABULATION: CORRESPONDENCE 1957 - 1958, TL, TLS (2) (Box-folder 17:024)
- CONSTRUCTION OF MULTI-STOREY ADDITION, BID TABULATION: ADVERTISEMENT 1957, TMs (Box-folder 17:025)
- LIST OF BIDDERS FOR MULTI-STOREY ADDITION TO UVA HOSPITAL 1958, TMs (Box-folder 17:026)
- BID PROPOSALS FOR CONSTRUCTION OF MULTI-STOREY ADDITION TO UVA HOSPITAL January 28, 1958, TMs (Box-folder 17:027)
- BID TABULATIONS FOR MULTI-STOREY ADDITION 1958, TMs (Box-folder 17:028)
- FORM OF AGRREEMENT BETWEEN UVA & MARENKA METAL MANUFACTURING CO. February 14, 1958, Doc (Box-folder 17:029)
- FORM OF AGREEMENT BETWEEN UVA & IVY CONSTRUCTION CORP. February 1958, Doc, TMs (Box-folder 17:030)
  RE: CONSTRUCTION OF MULTI-STOREY ADDITION TO UVA HOSPITAL
- FORM OF AGREEMENT BETWEEN UVA AND AMERICAN STERILIZER CO. February 1958, Doc. (Box-folder 17:031)
- STANDARD PERFORMANCE BOND February 1958, Doc. (Box-folder 17:032)
- CONSTRUCTION OF MULTI-STOREY ADDITION, CAPITAL OUTLAY STUDY 1953 - 1954; 1960, TL, TMs (Box-folder 17:033)
  INCLUDES CORRESPONDENCE
- CONSTRUCTION OF MULTI-STOREY ADDITION, CHANGE ORDERS: CORRESPONDENCE 1958, TL (2), TLS (2) (Box-folder 17:034)
- CONSTRUCTION OF MULTI-STOREY ADDITION, CHANGE ORDERS: CORRESPONDENCE January 1959 - April 1959, TL, TLS (2) (Box-folder 17:035)
- CONSTRUCTION OF MULTI-STOREY ADDITION, CHANGE ORDERS: CORRESPONDENCE May 1959 - December 1959, TL, TLS (2) (Box-folder 17:036)
- CONSTRUCTION OF MULTI-STOREY ADDITION, CHANGE ORDERS: CORRESPONDENCE 1960, TLS (Box-folder 17:037)
- CHANGE ORDER PROCEDURE April 1958 - May 1958, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 17:038)
- CHANGE ORDER NO.16 May 1959, TMs, TLS, TL (Box-folder 17:039)
- CHANGE ORDERS NO. 24-25-26 June 1959, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 17:040)
  INCLUDES CORRESPONDECNE AND FLOOR PLANS
- CHANGE ORDER NO. KE-5; KITCHEN EQUIPMENT June 1959, TLS (2), TMs (Box-folder 17:041)
- CHANGE ORDERS NO. 27 & 28 June 1959, TMs, TLS (Box-folder 17:042)
- CHANGE ORDER NO. 29 July 1959, TLS (2), TMs (Box-folder 17:043)
- CHANGE ORDER NO. 30 July 1959, TMs, TLS (Box-folder 17:044)
- CHANGE ORDER NO. 31 August 1959, TMs, TLS (2) (Box-folder 17:045)
- CHANGE ORDERS NO. 33-34-35-36 October 1959, TMs, TLS (2) (Box-folder 17:046)
- CHANGE ORDER NO. 37 October 1959, TMs, TLS (2) (Box-folder 17:047)
- CHANGE ORDER NO. 38 November 1959, TMs, TLS (2) (Box-folder 17:048)
- CHANGE ORDERS NO. 40-41-42-43-44-45 December 1959, TMs, TLS (2) (Box-folder 17:049)
- CHANGE ORDERS NOS. 40-45 January 1960, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 17:051)
- CHANGE ORDERS NOS. 46-47 January 1960, TLS (2), TMs (Box-folder 17:051)
- CHNAGE ORDERS NO. 46 -47 January 1960, TMs, TLS (2) (Box-folder 17:052)
- CHANGE ORDERS NO. 48 February 1960, TLS (2), TMs (Box-folder 17:053)
- CHANGE ORDER NO. 49 February 1960, TMs, TLS (2) (Box-folder 17:054)
- CHNAGE ORDER NO. 50 April 1960, TMs, TLS (2) (Box-folder 17:055)
- CHANGE ORDERS NO. 51-52 May 1960, TMs, TLS (2) (Box-folder 17:056)
- CHNAGE ORDER NO. 52 April 1960, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 17:057)
- CHNAGE ORDER NO. 1, STERILIZING EQUIPMENT May 1960, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 17:058)
- CHNAGE ORDER NO. KE-6, KITCHEN EQUIPMENT May 1960, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 17:059)
- CHANGE ORDERS NO. 53 - 54 June 1960, TMs, TLS (3) (Box-folder 17:060)
- CHANGE ORDER NO. 55 July 1960, TMs, TLS (2) (Box-folder 17:061)
- CHANGE ORDER NO. 57 September 1960, TMs, TLS (2) (Box-folder 17:062)
- CHANGE ORDER NO. 58 October 1960, TMs, TLS (2) (Box-folder 17:063)
- CHANGE ORDER NO. 59 October 1960, TMs, TLS (2) (Box-folder 17:064)
- CHANGE ORDER NO. KE-7, KITCHEN EQUIPMENT October 1960, TLS (Box-folder 17:065)
- CHANGE ORDERS NO. 60-61 November 1960, TMs, TLS (2) (Box-folder 17:066)
- CHANGE ORDERS NO. 62, 63, AND 64 December 1960, TMs, TLS (2) (Box-folder 17:067)
- CONSTRUCTION OF MULTI-STOREY ADDITION: CONFERENCE MEMORANDA October 1956, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 18:001)
- CONSTRUCTION OF MULTI-STOREY ADDITION: CONFERENCE MEMORANDA November 1956, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 18:002)
- CONSTRUCTION OF MULTI-STOREY ADDITION: CONFERENCE MEMORANDA December 1956, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 18:003)
- CONSTRUCTION OF MULTI-STOREY ADDITION: CONFERENCE MEMORANDA January - February 1957, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 18:004)
- CONSTRUCTION OF MULTI-STOREY ADDITION: CONFERENCE MEMORANDA March 1957 - July 1957, TMs, TLS (2) (Box-folder 18:005)
- CONSTRUCTION OF MULTI-STOREY ADDITION: CONTINGENCY FUND ACCOUNT SHEETS 1954 - 1960, TMs (Box-folder 18:006)
- CONSTRUCTION COSTS OF MULTI-STOREY ADDITION: CORRESPONDENCE 1956, TLS (2), TL, AMs (Box-folder 18:007)
- CONSTRUCTION COSTS OF MULTI-STOREY ADDITION: CORRESPONDENCE 1959 - 1960, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 18:008)
- DEDICATION OF MULTI-STOREY ADDITION: MINUTES AND CORRESPONDENCE 1960 - 1961, TL, TMs (Box-folder 18:009)
- CONSTRCUTION OF MULTI-STOREY ADDITION, EQUIPMENT: CORRESPONDENCE 1955 - 1960, TLS (2), TMs (Box-folder 18:010)
- FINISH ABBREVIATIONS, MULTI-STOREY ADDITION, UVA HOSPITAL December 1956, TMs (Box-folder 18:011)
- SUPPLEMENTARY CAPITAL OUTLAY, GROUP II AND III EQUIPMENT LIST September 1960, TMs (Box-folder 18:012)
  FROM FINISH ABBREVIATIONS FILE
- ROOM LEGEND SHEET TO MULTI-STOREY ADDITION, UVA HOSPITAL 1960, TMs (Box-folder 18:016)
- GROUP II EQUIPMENT LIST TO MULTI-STOREY ADDITION, UVA HOSPITAL 1960, TL, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 18:017)
- CONSTRUCTION OF MULTI-STOREY ADDITION: MINUTES AND REPORT OF HOSPITAL BUILDING COMMITTEE September 1954, TMs (Box-folder 18:018)
- CONSTRUCTION OF MULTI-STOREY ADDITION: CORRESPONDENCE 1958, TL, TLS (2) (Box-folder 18:019)
  RE: INSURANCE
- CONSTRUCTION OF MULTI-STOREY ADDITION, KITCHEN: CORRESPONDENCE 1951 - 1956, TL, TLS (2), TMs, ALS (Box-folder 18:020)
- CONSTRUCTION OF MULTI-STOREY ADDITION, KITCHEN: CORRESPONDENCE 1957, TMs, TLS (2) (Box-folder 18:021)
- CONSTRUCTION OF MULTI-STOREY ADDITION, KITCHEN: CORRESPONDENCE 1958 - 1960, TL, TLS (2), TMs (Box-folder 18:022)
- CONSTRUCTION OF MULTI-STOREY ADDITION, LIFE SCIENCE BUILDING: CORRESPONDENCE January 12, 1956, TLS (Box-folder 18:023)
- ROUGH DRAFT: OUTLINE SPECIFICATIONS FOR MULTI STOREY ADDITION May 15, 1956, TMs (Box-folder 18:024)
- OUTLINE SPECIFICATIONS FOR MULTI-STOREY ADDITION, UVA HOSPITAL July 31, 1956, TMs (Box-folder 18:025)
- CONSTRUCTION OF MULTI-STOREY ADDITION, UVA HOSPITAL, PNEUMATIC TUBE SYSTEM: CORRESPONDENCE 1961, TL, TLS (2) (Box-folder 18:026)
- CONSTRUCTION OF ULTI-STOREY ADDITION, UVA HOSPITAL, RADIOLOGY BUILDING: CORRESPONDENCE 1954 - 1956, ALS, TL (2), TLS (2) (Box-folder 18:027)
- CONSTRUCTION OF MULTI-STOREY ADDITION, UVA HOSPITAL, RADIOLOGY BUILDING: CORRESPONDENCE 1957 - 1958, TL, TLS (2) (Box-folder 18:028)
- CONSTRUCTION OF MULTI-STOREY ADDITION, UVA HOSPITAL, RADIOLOGY BUILDING: CORRESPONDENCE February - April 1959, TL (2), TLS (2) (Box-folder 18:029)
- CONSTRUCTION OF MULTI-STOREY ADDITION, UVA HOSPITAL, RADIOLOGY BUILDING: CORRESPONDENCE May 1959 - May 1961, TL, TLS (2) (Box-folder 18:030)
- CONSTRUCTION OF MULTI-STOREY BUILDING, UVA HOSPITAL, STERILIZERS: CORRESPONDENCE 1957 - 1959, TL, TLS (2), TMs (Box-folder 18:031)
- CONSTRUCTION OF MULTI-STOREY ADDITION, UVA HOSPITAL, STERILIZERS: CORRESPONDENCE 1960 - 1962, TL, TLS (2) (Box-folder 18:032)
- CONSTRUCTION OF NEURO-PSYCHIATRIC ADDITION: CORRESPONDENCE 1953 - 1956, TL (2) (Box-folder 18:033)
- CONSTRUCTION, PHASE I: CORRESPONDENCE 1954 - 1955, TL, TLS (Box-folder 18:034)
- CONSTRUCTION PHASE I, FIREPROOFING AND REMODELING: CORRESPONDENCE 1957, AN, TN, TLS (Box-folder 18:035)
- CONSTRUCTION PHASE II: CORRESPONDENCE 1958 - 1961, TL, TLS (2), TMs (Box-folder 18:036)
- CONSTRUCTION PHASE II: CORRESPONDENCE 1962 - 1966, TL, TLS (2) (Box-folder 18:037)
- AMENDMENT TO CONTRACT WITH BASKERVILLE & SON, ARCHITECTS 1960, TL (Box-folder 18:038)
  FROM CONSTRUCTION PHASE II FILE
- CONSTRUCTION PHASE II, ALTERATIONS AND ADDITIONS: CORRESPONDENCE 1959 - 1960, TL, TLS (2) (Box-folder 18:039)
- CONSTRUCTION PHASE II, ALTERATIONS AND ADDITIONS: CORRESPONDENCE 1961, TL, TLS (2) (Box-folder 18:040)
- CONSTRUCTION PHASE II, ALTERATIONS AND ADDITIONS: CORRESPONDENCE February - March 1962, TL, TLS (2), TMs (Box-folder 18:041)
- CONSTRUCTION PHASE II, ALTERATIONS AND ADDITIONS: CORRESPONDENCE April 1962 -December 1962, TL, TLS (2), TMs (Box-folder 18:042)
- CONSTRUCTION PHASE II, ALTERATIONS AND ADDITIONS: CORRESPONDENCE 1963, TL, TLS (2) (Box-folder 18:043)
- CONSTRUCTION PHASE II, CAPITAL OUTLAY: CORRESPONDENCE April 12, 1962, TL (Box-folder 18:044)
- CONSTRUCTION PHASE II, CHANGE ORDERS 1-7 1962 - 1963, TL, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 18:045)
- CONSTRUCTION PHASE II, CLINICAL DEPARTMENTS OFFICE BUILDING: CORRESPONDENCE 1961, TL, TMs, TLS (2) (Box-folder 18:046)
- CONSTRUCTION PHASE II, CLINICAL DEPARTMENTS OFFICE BUILDING: CORRESPONDENCE 1962 - 1964, TL, TLS (2) (Box-folder 18:047)
- CONSTRUCTION PHASE II, CLINICAL RESEARCH FACILITIES: CORRESPONDENCE 1956 - 1961, TL, TLS (2) (Box-folder 18:048)
- CONSTRUCTION PHASE II, FIREPROOFING AND REMODELING: CORRESPONDENCE October - December 1960, TL, TLS (2), TMs (Box-folder 18:049)
- CONSTRUCTION PHASE II, FIREPROOFING AND REMODELING: CORRESPONDENCE 1961 - 1962, TL (2), TLS (2), TMs (Box-folder 18:050)
- CONSTRUCTION PHASE II, MECHANICAL MODIFICATIONS: CORRESPONDENCE 1963, TLS (Box-folder 18:051)
- CONSTRUCTION PHASE II: MEDICAL RESEARCH ADDITION November 11, 1960, TLS (Box-folder 18:052)
- CONSTRUCTION PHASE II, PART I: CORRESPONDENCE C 1964, TL, TLS (Box-folder 18:053)
- ESTIMATE OF COSTS: HOSPITAL PHASE II, PART I AND PROJECT SCHEDULE December 1961 - Oct. 1962, TL, TMs (Box-folder 18:054)
- CONSTRUCTION PHASE II, PART I, CLINICAL DEPARTMENTS OFFICE BUILDING: CORRESPONDENCE 1963 - 1964, TL, TLS (Box-folder 18:055)
- CONSTRUCTION PHASE II, PART I: PROGRESS REPORT January 1964, TL, TMs (Box-folder 18:056)
- CONSTRUCTION PHASE II, PART II: CORRESPONDENCE 1962 - 1964, TL, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 18:057)
- CONSTRUCTION PHASE II, PART II, ALTERATIONS AND ADDITIONS: CORRESPONDENCE 1961 - 1964, TL, TLS (2), TMs (Box-folder 18:058)
- CAPITAL OUTLAY EUQIPMENT LIST September 1965, TL, TMs (Box-folder 18:059)
- CONSTRUCTION PHASE II, PART II, CLINICAL DEPARTMENTS OFFICE BUILDING: CORRESPONDENCE 1964 - 1966, TL, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 19:001)
- CONSTRUCTION PHASE II, PART II, UROLOGY DEPARTMENT: CORRESPONDENCE 1964, TL, TLS (2) (Box-folder 19:002)
- CONSTRUCTION PHASE II: PROGRESS REPORTS 1962 - 1963, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 19:003)
- CONSTRUCTION PHASE II, PROJECT REPORT August 1954, TMs (Box-folder 19:004)
- CONSTRUCTION PHASE III, OUTPATIENT DEPARTMENT AND CLINICAL SERVICES BUILDING: CORRESPONDENCE 1969, TL (Box-folder 19:005)
- CONSTRUCTION, PRIVATE PRACTICE COMMITTEE: MINUTES AND CORRESPONDENCE 1959 - 1960, TL, TMs (Box-folder 19:006)
- FIRST REPORT OF THE PRIVATE PRACTICE COMMITTEE January 26, 1960, TMs (Box-folder 19:007)
- CONSTRUCTION: PROJECT APPLICATIONS 1952 - 1958, TLS (Box-folder 19:008)
- CONSTRUCTION: PROJECT SHEDULES 1954 - 1961, TL, TLS (2), TMs (Box-folder 19:009)
- CONSTRUCTION: PROPOSED SPECIAL PROJECT PROGRAM, SCHEDULE AND COSTS 1953 - 1954, TMs (Box-folder 19:010)
- CONSTRUCTION OF PSYCHIATRY DEPARTMENT: CORRESPONDENCE C 1962, TL (Box-folder 19:011)
- CONSTRUCTION-RENOVATIONS: PROFESSIONAL COST CONTRACT March 1954 - April 1954, TDs, TLS (Box-folder 19:012)
- CONSTRUCTION OF RUCKER FUND ALTERATION SCHEDULE 1953, TMs (Box-folder 19:013)
- CONSTRUCTION, SPECIAL SERVICES CORRESPONDENCE March 1981 - May 1981, TL (2), TN, TLS, AN (Box-folder 19:014)
- CONSTRUCTION, SPECIAL SERVICES: DIRECTORY INFORMATION, PRELIMINARY DRAFT DATA 1981, TL, TMs (Box-folder 19:015)
- A DIRECTORY OF CONSULTATION AND SPECIAL SERVICES 1980 1980, Pamphlet (Box-folder 19:016)
  FROM CONSTRUCTION OF SPECIAL SERVICES FILE
- CONSTRUCTION, SYRINGES: CORRESPONDENCE July, December 1955, TL (2) (Box-folder 19:017)